

AKASH BHOVI

Motion designer & Video editor

My Portfolio

Contacts

- •
- +91 7338201038
- akashfx26@gmail.com
- Akash Bhovi

Expertise

- Video editing
- Motion graphics
- 3D animation
- Graphic designing
- Management Skills
- Leadership
- Digital Marketing
- Web development

Tools

- Adobe after effects
- Adobe Premier pro
- Blender
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator

Language

- English
- Kannada
- Hindi

About Me

I'm a Motion designer and Video editor with 5 years of experience creating videos that connect with audiences. My storytelling skills and attention to detail have proven to increase ROI, driving leads and app downloads through successful campaigns.

Experience

Video Editor & Motion Designer

Hashfame | 2024 - Present

- Collaborated with creative and marketing teams to produce innovative content.
- Worked on Meta ads, campaign execution, PR content, Social Media and website motion graphics.
- Delivered 60% ROI and doubled app downloads post-campaign.
- Used After Effects, Premiere Pro, Photoshop, Illustrator, and Figma for high-quality visuals.

Freelance Video Editor

Self-employed | 2020 - 2024

- Produced high-quality videos for content creators and tech companies aimed at their target audience..
- Managed video production, including editing, sound design, and visual effects.
- Developed creative concepts and scripts to enhance storytelling.
- · Delivered projects on time and within budget.

Education

Bachelor of Computer Application (BCA)

Mangalore University | MGM college, Udupi 2021 - 2024

Achievements

- Crossed 10k followers in instagram..
- Reached 1M accounts within 30 days

Certification

- campaign design for SM
- Master in video ads making
- Unlock typography